<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ali Molajani</title>
    <link>https://ali-molajani.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ali Molajani</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 01:09:59 +0430</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ali-molajani.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Distribution of choice</title>
      <link>https://ali-molajani.github.io/posts/my_distro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 01:09:59 +0430</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ali-molajani.github.io/posts/my_distro/</guid>
      <description>I chosed my GNU/Linux distribution! If you&amp;rsquo;ve been a GNU/Linux user you should be aware of GNU/Linux distribution and their variety. This feature make GNU/Linux kind of spcial because it can give a wide range of options and also make it confusing for the beginners to start working with GNU/Linux.
How do i reach the conclusion? Well like most of the GNU/Linux users i hop over few GNU/Linux distributions. My first distro was Ubuntu it was solid and i really like the Unity desktop environment (nowadays Ubuntu ships with Gnome desktop env which is not my favorite!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://ali-molajani.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 16:15:50 +0430</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ali-molajani.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: I am ali molajani student of the MS of the nanoelectronics at Shahid beheshti university in tehran. My intersts are mainly around the Electronics Eng. and programming and using different languages and frame works specially C/C++, Rust, even Linux source code.
Why you need a site? Some times i really sense to share my thoughts and discoveries in tech with people because i see problems that can engage them and consumes thier time due to lack of experience where here we hope can do our best to show case newer and more efficient frameworks or technologies to make everyone&amp;rsquo;s life a little bit easier.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
